I am a UX Designer who has spent the last 7 years working in various capacities in research and writing. My background working for small businesses provides me with the experience of managing mid-stage business development, while my practical understanding of front-end development allows me to operate concurrently with developers in agile or lean frameworks to effectively execute design sprints.

Skills

UX Skills:

A/B Testing, Ethnographic/User Research, C&C Analysis, Card Sorting, Contextual Inquiry, E-Commerce, Heuristic Evaluation, Information Architecture, Journey Mapping, Personas, SWOT Analysis, User Scenarios, Wireframes

UI Skills:

Branding, Logo/Icon Design, Modular Design, Prototyping, Sketching, User-Centered Design, Web & Mobile Design (Adaptive & Responsive Web)

Tools:

Adobe CC (XD, Illustrator, PhotoShop), Figma, Invision, Jira, Marvel, MS Office, Shopify, Sketch, Zeplin

Professional Experience

(Freelance) Dec. 2018 - Present

UX/UI Designer | Researcher

Work with a variety of clients and their teams to conduct research, validate, and develop all design elements, ranging from product to interface.

- Responsible for design, wireframes, prototyping, documentation, and iteration.
- Constant collaboration with stakeholders and developers to ensure that goals are met with quality.

Distillery Oct. 2018 - Nov. 2018

UX/Product Designer

Distillery is a full-service software development company recognized for their work in large-scale enterprises as well as mobile applications spanning areas such as finance, lifestyle, and gaming.

- Utilized scrum framework to work with client and development team.
- Worked closely with product manager to develop UX roadmap and statement of work.
- Conducted C&C analyses with competitors as well as businesses utilizing similar software.
- Prepared and led user interviews during 1-week user research sprint.
- Conducted open card sorts to inform information architecture and hierarchy.
- Created PowerPoint presentations for weekly check-ins with client.
- Created a product site map and 3 user flows identifying the needs of each different user type.
- Created mid-fidelity wireframes to present to client and to assist UI designer with the creation of a style sheet.



Jobs for Hope (a Hack for LA project)

Jul. 2018 - Nov. 2018

UX/UI Designer | Logo Design | Front-End Development

'Jobs for Hope' is an open source civic project working to streamline the usability and search experience of skilled individuals seeking jobs through the Los Angeles County Homeless Initiative.

- Worked alongside developers to determine build limitations and execution strategies in preparation for 2-week design sprint.
- Manually scraped current 'Jobs' section for region-specific job entries to identify category trends and notable inconsistencies/redundancies between different organizations' job listings.
- Conducted usability tests of current site to identify user pain points when searching for a job as a 'Manager' and synthesizing test results with other UX researchers to inform feature prioritization.
- Created a high-fidelity wireframe and prototype to be presented to a director of the Los Angeles County Homeless Initiative to receive clearance to move forward with the project and development.
- Conducted a design studio to design a hexagonal badge/sticker to represent the Jobs for Hope project in the 2018 National Day of Civic Hacking.

Grid110 Aug. 2018 – Sep. 2018

UX Designer | Researcher

Grid110 is an economic and community-development accelerator program partnered with the Los Angeles Mayor's Office.

- Conducted C&C Analyses of existing database software and social platforms.
- Conducted user surveys to capture users who were unable to participate in user interviews.
- Conducted user interviews of Grid110 users over a 3-day research sprint.
- Synthesized response data to create a feature prioritization, user personas, and user flows.
- Created a paper prototype to conduct usability tests to validate initial assumptions.
- Built off existing branding guidelines to create a style guide for the application.
- Created a high-fidelity prototype to showcase a web-based user interface.
- Created a Google Slides presentation to present to product client and for client use.

Education

General Assembly, Downtown Los Angeles

Jun. 2018 - Aug. 2018

Certificate of Completion in UX Design, Research, Strategy

University of California, Los Angeles

Sep. 2013 - Jun. 2016

Bachelor of Arts in Anthropology, Specialization in Sociocultural Studies

Pasadena City College

Jun. 2007 - Jun. 2013

Associate of Arts in Social Sciences, Specialization in Anthropology Associate of Sciences in Paralegal Studies, Specialization in Legal Research (Certified)